chennaisuperkings.com 2018-03-15

# Chennai Super Kings

  | 

##  Privacy Policy

Chennai Super Kings is sensitive to privacy issues on the Internet. We believe it is important you know how we treat the information about you; we receive from you, on the Internet.

In general, you can visit www.chennaisuperkings.com on the World Wide Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our Web Servers collect the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, domain names, not the e-mail addresses of visitors. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. The Chennai Super Kings uses this information to measure the usability of our site and improve the content of our site. Accessing our site signifies your unconditional consent to allow the collection of your domain names.

We want you to feel confident about using www.chennaisuperkings.com to browse, become kings club member, purchase your match tickets and involve in store merchandizing, so we are committed to protect the information we collect. Usually, the personal information we collect is used only by us to respond to your inquiry, process an order, or allow you to access specific account information. Occasionally, we may make the e-mail addresses of those who provide information available to other reputable organizations whose services we think, you may find interesting. In these cases, you will be offered an opportunity to limit access to your information. In case we do not receive any response from you to limit the access of your information, it shall be deemed that you consent to such distribution of your information as mentioned above. While no website can guarantee security, we have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect the personal information you provide to us. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure correct use of information, we will employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies.

If you register with any one of the Chennai Super Kings' business units online, then they may use this information to provide you with custom information about Chennai Super Kings' offerings in support of your business needs.

A technology called Cookies may be used to provide you with tailored information. A Cookie is a tiny element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a Cookie. Registering with any Chennai Super Kings’ business unit online signifies your unconditional consent to receive such Cookies.

At times, we conduct on-line surveys to understand better the needs and profile of our visitors. When we conduct a survey, we will try (but are not obligated) to let you know how we will use the information at the time we collect information from you on the Internet.

You recognize and understand that there is no compulsion on you to provide us with your personal information, if any. All the personal information provided by you to us is with your full consent, own volition, and desire to provide such personal information. You also understand that we are under no obligation to verify the source from, which the personal information about you is provided to us, and they are deemed to be provided by you, unless you demonstrate to us within a period of 15 days from the date of providing of such information to us, to our satisfaction, that the information was provided to us without your free consent.

Chennai Super Kings website may contain links to other sites such as Chennai Super Kings’ partners and affiliates. While we try to link only to the sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by the other sites.  

---|---
